(Penny:)Yeah, call it whatever you want,
I get minimum wage.
(Penny:)Yeah.
(Penny:)I was wondering
if you could help me out...
(Leonard:)- Yes.
- Oh.
(Penny:)Okay, great, I'm having
some furniture delivered...
...and I may not be here, so, oh...
(Penny:)Hello.
[SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN]
(Penny:)I'm sorry?
(Howard:)Haven't you ever been told
how beautiful you are in flawless Russian?
- No, I haven't.
- Get used to it.
(Penny:)Yeah, I probably won't.
(Penny:)- Hey, Sheldon.
- Hi.
(Penny:)Hey, Raj.
(Penny:)Still not talking to me, huh?
(Sheldon:)Don't take it personally,
it's his pathology.
(Sheldon:)- He can't talk to women.
- He can't talk to attractive women.
(Howard:)Or in your case,
a cheesecake-scented goddess.
(Leonard:)- There's gonna be some furniture delivered?
- Yeah.
(Penny:)If it gets here and I'm not here,
could you sign for it and put it in?
(Leonard:)- Yeah, no problem.
- Great, here's my spare key.
(Penny:)Thank you.